MATTHEW VOLODZKO

Digital Marketing Manager

Profile

Highly experienced and trained for more than 8 years, specializing in SEO, web design, and social media.

Contact

(803) 415-3325 matt volodzko@

matt.volodzko@gmail.com ahobosapien.com/portfolio

Certifications

Google Analytics for Beginners Google Advanced Analytics Google Online Marketing Fundamentals Google Adwords Fundamentals

Google Adwords Fundamentals
Google Adwords Display
Google Adwords Search
Google Digital Unlocked
Hubspot Inbound
Hubspot Inbound Marketing
Hubspot Social Media
Udemy Complete Digital Marketing
Udemy Digital Marketing

Languages

Advanced Chinese Beginner Spanish

Masterclass

Publications

"How to Make Money Dropshipping on eBay"

"Authentic Chinese Cuisine"

Education

B.A. in International BuinessSouthern New Hampshire UniversitySep 2019

Experience

DIGITAL MARKETING MANAGER | VATC, EPIC Ready, & SOFWOLF

St. Petersburg, FL | Apr 2019 - Present

- · Lead in all digital marketing efforts and optimizations on 3 sites
- Plan, organize, create, and post on all social media accounts, & YouTube
- Plan & create for events, press, prints, & blog posts
- Increase clicks & impressions more than 100%
- Increase users & views more than 300%

SEO SPECIALIST | 51 Blocks

Remote | May 2019 - Present

- Perform numerous tasks such as keyword research and blog optimization
- Track & manage tasks using ClickUp & Slack
- Conduct monthly reviews of clients using GSC, GMB, & aDash

SEO SPECIALIST | Atigro

Remote | July 2019 - Present

- Perform weekly SEO tasks such as keyword research and content creation
- Create and implement 3 month plans involving on & off site SEO
- Track & analyze data with GSC, G Analytics, Data Studio, & Agency Analytics

Digital Marketing Specialist | Freelance

Remote | Aug 2013 - Apr 2019

- · Design sites using CSS, HTML, Wordpress, & Shopify
- Graphic design with Photoshop, Illustrator, & Canva
- Seo opt, competitor analysis, social media marketing, PPC, & email

Financial Crimes Specialist | Wells Fargo

Charlotte, NC | Jul 2017 - Sep 2-18

- Detect/prevent financial crime activity using multiple computer systems
- Acheived 99% accountability and 99.9% quality-assurance rates

Social Media Marketing Specialist | Social Giant

Remote | Sep 2016 - Jul 2017

- Acquire new leads through aggressive marketing techniques
- Assist the marketing teams with developing new strategies
- Utilize proprietary tools to increase awareness and to analyze performance

Digital Marketing Specialist | The One Hotel

China | May 2012 - Nov 2013

- Take over all marketing campaigns to obtain 3.89% conversion rate
- Responsible for over \$50K increased revenue during first two campaigns
- Transform low quality social media profile into substantial online presence

Digital Marketing Coordinator | Chiron

China | Jan 2010 - May 2012

- Lead the IT and graphic design teams in marketing efforts
- Spearhead all online marketing via WeChat and Weibo
- Acheive over 100% increase in customer acquisition in 2 months